There is so much sorrow in the world,
my sorrow is so
little, when I saw the sorrow of people [screaming sound] I
forgot my own sorrow [screaming sound].
100 three 100 three if it is just a murder then don't
say anything where you die 100 tomorrow it is
just a murder tomorrow if it is
not a
matter then make you unconscious
yes make you unconscious
stop me from doing it hanging is not the answer to the dacoit kill me throw me throw me
tomorrow then kill me throw me
[Music] she
said
yes Pappu tell me
yes you have
told me once then it is fine you are standing at
9 o'clock oh what to
say Pappu again there is a problem
Pappu tell me slow down have you
controlled yourself
[Music]
I am
not in this world but then it is
Karbula Haram so after all what can I say tell me
something
Pappu I did not say this but if you ask him then he
says
cut it every day it is just a matter Pappu if I
use wrong words to solve I love you first [laughs]
work
is fine come on friend
enough Lata son Lata fati son fati wife kick
son kick daughter-in-law listen listen
if you abuse me then son just abuse me abuse fati
son fati laate re son bring it
Hey, just open your mouth, you bastard, hit me, hit me, hit me, bastard, hit me,
bastard
[Music]
[Music] Get up, open your mouth, open your mouth
[Music] Spank me, you didn't light an incense stick [Music] [Music] [Music]
Hello,
yes Nanu,
yes,
then run away, son, you bastard, run, understand [Music] Now have you left me, hey, what, hey, don't marry me, do you understand [Music] yes, what is the problem with me, my daughter, you bastard, then run, run, catch me,
hey Pappu, then run, do your
work in the shop, if you want, then tell me I love you, it's
right, son, I love you, I love you, I love you, no, I love you, I love ...
Nice new
designer saree, Ila should wear this saree for your feast,
yes all of you should
eat at the feast, it's a
very nice saree, take whatever you want
[Music] nice saree,
yes nice saree, the look
and feel is
good, how far have you managed to
cover it up,
oh no, there is money below [Music] the
money below, one thing is the same as it used to be, today
we are wearing a designer saree, give money
below, nowadays no one goes shopping, it's not like that,
then
first buy a saree of equal size, then I have taken the
matter [Music]
if I get married, then go and
ask for money, if you don't ask then use your hand, if you don't agree then use your
kick, but get my
saree, you are a new model, I swear, eat something at the feast, all of you should eat at the
feast, I have been
working for 55 years, but I have
n't got a saree, go and buy it, yes no, go and buy it,
1500,
yes 1500, exactly the price
[Music]
ch [Music]
ba,
oh no  Abuse,
abuse, son, abuse, abuse,
oh my
brain, brain,
abuse
[laughter] I
explained, still you understand, you keep on
gossiping at night, you keep on beating yourself, you keep on
gossiping at
night [screaming sound]
man, did you understand, did you not understand
anything, then I
[music]
take the punch, take the punch, hit, hit, you could
not get it done [music]
hit me or get it done,
yes, beat me a lot, that is why you could not call me, then
son, do one thing, get it done,
son,
you have got it done,
go
[music] I am
counting the birds along with Bata, I am not leaving from here, my
work is not getting disturbed,
I am not going until I have the money, I have taken
one saree, I have not taken one saree, do something,
[music]
oh that saree,
sell your hen,
sell the hen, hen,
yes, now a bundle, now a bundle,
if not one, then you keep harassing
Daksh for five-six months,
talk to some boy, don't say, you
ruin him till the last [laughter] he is going to jail, his
shop, goods are stolen, here I got something, I ran away after having my fill
[music]
hey bari
Hey Badam goon Pappu my Barkira hen
sell your hen take it take the saree Aaka
the flute tuck the saree give the saree
I tuck it [Music] I do
n't have it right now and listen to me hey hey go ahead you are getting confused friend you are in
trouble
go
listen to me go and do it you can win
but my
stuff is too much [Music] I have a
lot of stuff my trick is too much my trick is too much
chain everything
customer advance money you have to pay even
water fake
helmet work
[Music] [Music]
drive the car slowly take tension tension
[Music]
straighten the pot now [
Music]
bad son bad stay calm go take
money today if you take money then
I won't bring any
ok Babu then I will cry
[Music]
come on just take a lot
Neelu Neel money
[Laughter] I have learnt
today I have learnt nothing I will leave you today bring more
[Music]
you understand yourself you understand yourself that Pappu is at
Pappu's place don't call him dead
[Screaming sound] who is he
hello
[Laughter] who is he
[screaming]
you bastard [laughter]
yes remember
my name is Nazrul Pappu bastard I have to say
who is my brother-in-law [screaming] I have a
lot of evil eyes hit me
[screaming] my friend
Pappu matter and matter you understand here here put the
number ta number ta say
yes
the number you are calling is my
mobile then tell me
give some other number friend no other
number
brother talk
[music]
hello
hey [screaming]
look
turn around
one came out
[music] if
people spend money on marriage then divorce
oh friend
you
give divorce
yes say but divorce is
always talked about if you spend 10 lakhs on marriage then
divorce
[laughter]
crazy man crazy man
animal
pay salary yes say you
listen just my sister no
yes you can't get divorce you should go there okay okay if you
work from Dubai now you will know
Come on, let's
go
with this Pappu [Music] There is no
kind of accident in this world, there is no kind of
accident, friend, there is no kind of matter,
so look at
this brother, brother, brother,
brother, I have been
carefree since childhood, Pappu,
yes, the stuff entered,
four-five sheets entered, entered from an angle,
show the angle, take out the boy got up,
any problem, I have a loan of one lakh, the police got up
right here
[Music]
Hey, tell me one thing, don't you walk
[Screaming voice] Yes, tell me the truth, if
not me, then don't do it, tell me quickly
[Laughter] Then what are you, what are you,
understand, Angana's shop became
money,
Hasan Hasan, how much
sorrow does he have in the world [Laughter]
my sorrow is so
little [Screaming voice] when I
saw the sorrow of the people [Screaming voice] did you
forget your sorrow, what is
your tension, see the tension,
brother, have you forgotten your tension, then what is your tension, hey,
tell me goon Pappu, earn a lot,
hot, I mean, I can't tolerate it
[Music]
Whose Pappu and Bali are talking here  What
is your name?  Yes
[music]
is that your name?   Yes.
Pappu's wife has
filed an FIR against Pappu and Boli.  And Pappu and
Boli are both of you.  So Babu, an
arrest warrant has been issued in the name of both of you, so
now you will have to go to jail Babu.  Out of which oppression
?
Under what oppression?  In case of domestic violence, you
beat your wife after drinking alcohol.  You
get your father to beat your wife.  You
torture me a lot.   Let me
talk about Satari.   Let's
not use unnecessary language.  Hey, catch it.   Let us go.
Hey sir sir sir sir come on sir.  Hey sir sir sir wait a minute
sir wait a minute sir wait a minute
hey mandri I am very proud of you you are the one who is in life
talk to me or run away with me my love
you get it done but inshallah I am from jail so
you when I make a promise in London but like a scoundrel
[laughs]
hold on to these words friend friend friend
understand it is a good
matter
understand it
but life is
from life
[music]